Hello, everyone.
I'm Sae Kanagawa from Nogizaka46.
Today, where am I?
I don't know.
Well, I went skiing.
It's been about three hours since I left Tokyo.
I'm just waking up from sleep.
Yes.
Yes, but I think today is the first time
I think today will be the first time you'll see me skiing.
I hope you're looking forward to it!
Okay, I'm going to get dressed now.
Let's go!
I love it. I love the wind.
It's super fun.
I'm dressed.
What do you think?
It's been a while since I've been here.
I'm a little nervous.
I'd like to ski properly from now on.
Well, I'm off now.
It's been so long, I'm scared.
Yes, sir.
Yay!
We did it!
That's great.
It's been a long time.
Long time no see.
Yay!
Oh, man, but I'm probably already dragging my feet.
I'm probably dragging my feet right now.
- It hurts like hell. Isn't there anyone here now? - Hey, great.
That's so good.
- That's great! How old have you been skiing?
I don't know. I was in kindergarten when I first started.
My dad took me to the advanced course.
It was really tough.
I remember crying while I was skiing.
I was practicing skiing with my father.
I was in A skiing class all through elementary school.
I wanted to be the best skier in my class, so it was really fun.
Is it getting windy?
I'm a bit of a cat person, so I have a microphone.
Microphone test.
It's warmer... because of this.
Here it comes!
Can you make it?
It's been 5 years since I've been here, but I'm going to do it right the first time.
Let's go!
Let's go! Let's go!
Wow!
Ew! That's scary!
Oh, man!
It's gonna be fun.
I'm off.
Yes, ma'am.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Oh, wow.
Oh, my God.
Okay, we're here.
Yeah!
I think I've got something for you.
My legs were already wobbling.
It was a lot of fun!
I'm already about 8% tired.
I used to go 5 or 6 times a year.
I went with my family and with my friend's mother.
I really liked it. I loved it. We were a family.
I loved it. We were a family, so I had my own skis and my own clothes.
I miss it so much.
But I've seen some pictures of them.
I remember that picture of Mr. Machi from kindergarten?
Mr. Machi? Mr. Machi?
I'm mixed up with Mr. Machi.
There was a picture of Mr. Nencho in a pink outfit.
There was a picture of him sitting there in a pink outfit, trying his best.
Where is he now?
It looks like there.
This is the beginner course, right?
This is the intermediate course.
Intermediate course?
Let's go to the intermediate course.
Is that a bell?
Yes, there's a bell.
Can I ring it?
Oh, my God, can I ring it?
Here we go.
I'll ring it.
What's that? Huh?
Whoa!
It rings.
Okay, okay.
Wow, it's beautiful. The sky.
Wow.
It's a little steeper than before.A little steeper than before.
Ah!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Are you okay?
Aah!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
A-ha-ha-ha!
Oh, shit.
Can you stand up?
I can stand.
Here we go.
Which way do I stand?
This way.
I got it.
Oh, no!
My first fall this year.
You want to do it?
Yes, sir.
Thank you for watching.
I love it. I love the wind.
Well, now that we've done Sunsbury.
Now I'm going to take a break and go get something to eat.
My stomach was growling the whole time.
I miss this walking.
I wonder what they have here.
What's in the burger? Looks delicious!
They started baked potatoes?
It says "Yaki-imo"... Looks delicious! Yaki-imo sounds good!
Which do you think is better, the nyaki or the cheeseburger? I can't decide today.
Thank you very much!
I got it!
Ta-da!
Looks delicious!
Bon appétit!
Oh!
Yum!
It's great after a workout!
It's the best after a workout!
Burger!
Teriyaki burger!
Thanks for the burger!
Yum! Delicious!
Can you tell? The meat is so thick!
So thick! And there's tomatoes.
Yum!
So now that we've finished our meal
I'd like to slide down the moon again!
Go!
Is it New Year's?
We had Osechi on New Year's Day.
I also ate a lot of oranges.
Also, my father bought me a fully automatic machine!
I think it's a very restful machine.
On the first day, it worked for about eight hours.
I do it for 8 hours at night.
I got a lot better at it.
I've been doing it with my family, and we've won first place and stuff.
Lately, I've been getting to know the roles.
You know, the ones with all the characters?
Twoissou.
Oh, is that right?
Yes, it's right.
I really love the "TSUISSAU".
And the dragon monk.
And the prairie...
Daisanjian, Daisanjian.
Daisanjian
I think of it as a prairie.
So I really enjoyed New Year's more than any other time of the year.
I enjoyed New Year's more than ever!
Let's go for the second half!
Quick!
Wow!
Yay!
Fun!
Great!
That's great! There's a cloud of planes!
Oh, my gosh! It's a good day to fly!
Bye-bye!
Okay, we're done.
It was so exhilarating, wasn't it?
It was so much fun that I felt as if all my tiredness from work just flew away.
That's great!
I finished skiing, but they have snowboarding too.
I'd like to try snowboarding for the first time.
Oh, no!
What? Wait a minute.
What do you mean?
I don't know, but I think it might be possible.
I don't know what it is, but there's a mysterious map.
I'd like to see if it's possible to ski like this.
I'd like to try it.
Yes, I've found it!
This is the back of the right foot, right?
You mean like this?
Oh, no!
Oh, no!Oh, shit!
We can do it.
I'm going, I'm going, I'm going, I'm going, I'm going, I'm going, I'm going.
It's impossible.
You can't do it.
I'm not scared.
Here we go.
Oh, my God.
What? Is it really this hard to squeeze in?
Go! Go for it!
No!
I'm all messed up.
Like this.
So? Yes!
Yes!
It stopped!
Oh, no!
What? But I feel like it was so close.
Let's get you to the other side so we can skate anyway.
Here! Here! Ah! Here it comes! Oh, no!
Yes, sir.
But doesn't he have good taste?
Oh, you think it's good?
Let's go.
I'll get some bears.
Wait a minute.
Wow!
I just did.
It's done!
It's done! It's done!
Oh, my God!
My butt hurts so much, but I did it!
I'm so happy!
I was surprised myself.
I was kind of switching sides at the end, wasn't I?
Ha-ha!
I was surprised myself.
I'm glad.
It was miraculously done!
So, I finished snowboarding.
I think I was able to enjoy skiing for the first time in about 5 years, and I'm very happy to be able to see you all for the first time.
I'm so happy that everyone could see me for the first time, and I also had a great time trying snowboarding at the end.
I'm so happy that I was able to ski well at the end.
So thank you all for watching! Please subscribe to my channel and click the "Good" button!
Bye bye!